no, because people
already don't have
as much connection
as they would
like to have.
It's not like
this is replacing
some sort of
better physical
connection that they
would've otherwise had.
It's that the
average person would
like to have
10 friends,
and they have
two or three.
And there's
just more demand
to socialize than
what people are
able to do
given the current
construct.
And giving people
the ability to
be present with
people who are
in other places
physically just seems
like it will
unlock more.
If I have
glasses, it's not
going to make
it that I
spend less time
with my wife.
It's going to
make it so
that I spend
more time with
my sister who
lives across the
country.
And I think
that that's good,
and I think
people need that.